let savollar29 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "bomb",
      answer: "C. bomba",
      options: [
        "A. sovg'a",
        "B. asbob",
        "C. bomba",
        "D. o'yinchoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "certificate",
      answer: "D. sertifikat",
      options: [
        "A. kundalik",
        "B. hisob-kitob",
        "C. jurnal",
        "D. sertifikat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "circumstance",
      answer: "A. vaziyat",
      options: [
        "A. vaziyat",
        "B. umid",
        "C. orzu",
        "D. tavakkal"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "coffin",
      answer: "B. tobut",
      options: [
        "A. ko'chma",
        "B. tobut",
        "C. chemodan",
        "D. shkaf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to cope",
      answer: "C. yengmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yo'qotmoq",
        "B. qo'rqmoq",
        "C. yengmoq",
        "D. chetlab o'tmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "criticism",
      answer: "A. tanqid",
      options: [
        "A. tanqid",
        "B. maqtash",
        "C. ruhiyat",
        "D. taklif"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to devastate",
      answer: "B. vayron qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qurilish qilmoq",
        "B. vayron qilmoq",
        "C. tiklash",
        "D. yaratmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to frown",
      answer: "D. xo'mraymoq",
      options: [
        "A. kuylamoq",
        "B. kulmoq",
        "C. quvonmoq",
        "D. xo'mraymoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to gaze",
      answer: "A. tikilib qaramoq",
      options: [
        "A. tikilib qaramoq",
        "B. unutmoq",
        "C. ko'zdan kechirmoq",
        "D. e'tibor bermagan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to glance",
      answer: "C. nazar tashlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. o'rganmoq",
        "B. tekshirmoq",
        "C. nazar tashlamoq",
        "D. chuqurroq o'rganmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "grief",
      answer: "B. qayg'u",
      options: [
        "A. quvonch",
        "B. qayg'u",
        "C. hayajon",
        "D. umid"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "groom",
      answer: "C. kuyov",
      options: [
        "A. kelin",
        "B. xizmatkor",
        "C. kuyov",
        "D. og'a"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "license",
      answer: "D. litsenziya",
      options: [
        "A. sir",
        "B. shartnoma",
        "C. qonun",
        "D. litsenziya"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "microscope",
      answer: "A. mikroskop",
      options: [
        "A. mikroskop",
        "B. teleskop",
        "C. kamera",
        "D. binokl"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "nuclear",
      answer: "C. yadroviy",
      options: [
        "A. tabiy",
        "B. organik",
        "C. yadroviy",
        "D. kimyoviy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to portray",
      answer: "B. tasvirlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. ochib bermoq",
        "B. tasvirlamoq",
        "C. yashirmoq",
        "D. uydirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to rotate",
      answer: "A. aylanmoq",
      options: [
        "A. aylanmoq",
        "B. to'xtatmoq",
        "C. bekitmoq",
        "D. qattiq turmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "souvenir",
      answer: "C. suvenir",
      options: [
        "A. asbob",
        "B. hujjat",
        "C. suvenir",
        "D. pul"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "submarine",
      answer: "B. suv osti kemasi",
      options: [
        "A. vertalyot",
        "B. suv osti kemasi",
        "C. samalyot",
        "D. kema"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to trace",
      answer: "D. andoza olmoq",
      options: [
        "A. chizmoq",
        "B. yo'qotmoq",
        "C. yashirmoq",
        "D. andoza olmoq"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar29;